(Amy:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Using Kolinar to suppress
my anger at that last comment.
(Amy:)Is it possible that your
concern for me at this moment
(Amy:)is motivated by nothing more
than simple jealousy?
(Sheldon:)I hadn't considered that.
(Sheldon:)Give me a moment.
(Sheldon:)All right, I've considered it.
(Amy:)And?
I reject it.
(Amy:)You reject it because
you don't feel jealousy,
(Amy:)or because you are
suppressing jealousy?
(Sheldon:)I think
I'll eat my lunch at home.
(Amy:)That's not your
lunch, Sheldon;
(Amy:)those are the cadaver
brain specimens.
(Bernadette:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)As they were incorrectly sliced,
(Sheldon:)you can see how I could
mistake them for my sashimi.
(Amy:)Hello.